

PROFILE

I am a self-taught Front-End Web Developer. Spending most of the quarantine time (10 months) in the USA by myself taught me how to stand on my foot. By looking at life from different angles, I finally found my passion for skiing and coding. Having worked with different types of groups such as project teams, nongovernmental organizations, and workplaces, improved my communication and organization skills, provide different aspects, and made me fluent in English. I code on CSS3 with Bootstrap, JavaScript (ES5, ES6), and currently working on Angular and React.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+90 (535) 012 05 79

WEBSITE:

alperenaydin.me

EMAIL:

alperen.aydin.work@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Skiing Coding Traveling

LINKS

GITHUB: github.com/ThisIsAlperen

LINKEDLN: linkedin.com/in/alperenaydına79355158/

ALPEREN AYDIN

Web Developer - Astronautical Engineer

EDUCATION

ISTANBUL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

2017 - PRESENT
2.7 GPA
Worked on 2 different project teams
Former board member of SAVTEK student club

WORK EXPERIENCE

SAV-SAT Satellite Competition Team - Organizer

September 2019–March 2020

I was responsible from reporting, scheduling and keeping the team together by solving the possible problems. At the same time, I was a member of the mechanical design team.

SAVTEK Student Club – Event Coordinator

February 2018 - March 2020

I did many works at this community, before pandemic, my main job was coordinating our annual and biggiest event with more than 1500 participant.

Whitefish Mountain Resort – Utility Staff

June 2020-March 2021

Mainly keeping the place running by working in a wide range from a cashier to barista.

SKILLS

